iam-architect.com 2014-11-21

# PRIVACY POLICY Iam Architect

### Privacy Policy

At [Iam Architect](http://www.iam-architect.com/), we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personal information you may provide us through our Website.

This Privacy Policy explains what information may be collected on [Iam Architect](http://www.iam-architect.com/), how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties.

### The Information We Collect and How We Use It

Our Website typically collects two types of information about you:

  * **Information that you provide that personally identifies you**

If you send us an e-mail or a comment, you may choose to provide us with personal information, such as your name or your e-mail address. We use the information to improve our service to you, provide you with updates, or to respond to your requests.

Whether or not you provide this information is your choice; however, in many instances this type of information is required to participate in the particular activity, realize a benefit we may offer, or gain access to certain content on our Website.

  * **Information that does not personally identify you, that we automatically collect when you visit our Website**

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We typically collect and store details about your visit, such as the Internet domain (for example, â€œwebsite.comâ€? if you use a private Internet access account), your IP address address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web), the type of browser and operating system used to access our site, the pages you visit, the date and time you access our Website and if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website.

We use the information we collect to count the number and type of visitors to the different pages on our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors like you.

### Keeping Your Information Secure

We have implemented security measures we consider reasonable and appropriate to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information. From time to time we evaluate new technology for protecting information, and when appropriate, we upgrade our information security systems.

Cookies

To save you comment’s information every time you visit [Iam Architect](http://www.iam-architect.com/), we place a little text file called a â€œcookieâ€? on your hard drive. It sits in your web browser directory.

A cookie lets us store your profile information on your computer and lets our website retrieve it when you visit our site. No other website can use or view the cookie set by [Iam Architect](http://www.iam-architect.com/).

Cookies help us create a speedy web experience by remembering your address and email information, so you don’t have to re-type it when making comments.

We may use cookies on the website for the purpose of monitoring your and other users’ activity in order to improve the website and the services available to you. If you don’t want us to use cookies when you use our website, you will need to change your Internet browser settings so that your browser does not accept them.

### Links to Other sites

[Iam Architect](http://www.iam-architect.com/) has links to partners and other sites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new website.

### Restriction of Liability

**Iam-Architect.com  **makes no claims, promises or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this website and expressly disclaims liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this website.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change some of the statements in this Privacy Policy at any time. We will prominently post notice of the changes at this URL. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective when posted.

Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.iam-architect.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.iam-architect.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.iam-architect.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.iam-architect.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.iam-architect.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.iam-architect.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.iam-architect.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### Share and Enjoy
